# PATRICIA CARR

PERSONAL WEBSITE: https://pcarrhi.github.io

## ABOUT

Thanks to a startup experience managing all the Communication activities, I helped develop a brand's identity from early stages to maturity in the IoT industry.

I also had the chance to work alongside Recruiting, R&D, and Sales teams to collaborate on multiple projects, which is where my open mindset and team spirit came into play.

My curiosity and ambition contributed to a proactive transition into Web Development where I challenged myself to learn new languages and gain new technical skills. At Altran I was able to have en enriching experience working with talented Developers and Project Managers for top industrial client applications.

# CONTACT

- +33 (0)6 51 82 03 56
- pcarr.hi@gmail.com
- Toulouse, France

# EDUCATION

# **Coding Academy by EPITECH**

(European Institute of Technology)
Full Stack Web Development
Oct 2019-July 2020

## **University of Hawaii at Manoa**

BA Communications & French, 2013 French Honor Society, Lambda Pi Eta

## SKILLS

### Marketing/Tools:

- Google Analytics
- Copywriting
- PR / Presentations
- MS Office
- Agile Framework
   (JIRA and Confluence)

#### Programming experience:

- Angular 8/9
- HTML5/CSS3/Styled
- React
- Components
- Python
- Firebase
- Mongo, Express, Node, React

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **WEB DEVELOPER INTERN**

#### **ALTRAN (PART OF CAPGEMINI)**

MARCH 2020- JULY 2020 - TOULOUSE, FRANCE

- Work with project managers and other developers to understand each feature and time of completion to build components
- Review and utilize existing codebase to correct Front-End bug problems with team using Angular 8 and React
- Communicate with teammates on daily basis regarding code or technical issues

#### **COMMUNICATIONS MANAGER**

#### **UWINLOC**

JUN 2016- JUN 2019 - TOULOUSE, FRANCE

- Act as a Business Development representative when meeting new prospects by conducting presentations/pitchs to acquire new partnerships in France and within EU, USA, Japan, China.
- Establish a Communication Plan for lead generation
- Create storyboards, online content, and Press Releases
- Manage social media content and report on KPIs
- Handle all external communication relations: press, print, graphic art, B2B event organizers
- Maintain relations with journalists & Press
- Organize event logistics to maximize visibility at trade shows

## **PROJECT COORDINATOR**

#### **ALLIANCE FOUNDATION TRIALS**

JULY 2014 - OCT 2015 - BOSTON, USA

- Document management for clinical online portal
- Event Logistics Support Biannual Pharma trade show
- Meeting Minutes for Executive Board
- · Feasibility study tracking for CRMs